Guide to the Jesse H. Jones Corporate and Property records, 1836-2008 MS 621
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Property Records, 234181
  - Harris County: South Side of Buffalo Bayou (SSBB)
    - Block 139
      - National Standard Building Leases, 1934-1935 (Box 194, Folder 16)
      - National Standard Building Leases, 1936-1937 (Box 194, Folder 17)
      - National Standard Building Leases, 1938-1941 (Box 194, Folder 18)
      - National Standard Building; Tenant Bankruptcy, 1946 (Box 194, Folder 19)
      - C&I Building Operating Account #1, 1951-1964 (Box 194, Folder 20)
        - Operating Account #1, 1951-1964 (Box 193, Folder 3-5)
      - C&I Building Operating Account #2, 1951-1964 (Box 194, Folder 21)
        - Operating Account #2, 1951-1964 (Box 195, Folder 1-2)
      - C&I Building Closed Accounts, 1951-1964 (Box 194, Folder 22-24)
      - C&I Building Accounts Receivable, 1951-1953 (Box 194, Folder 25)
      - C&I Building Building Ledger, 1964-1973 (Box 194, Folder 26)
        - Ledger, 1963-1973 (Box 195, Folder 3-5)
      - C&I Building Operating Account Transfer, 1964-1979 (Box 194, Folder 27, Box 196, Folder 1-3)
      - C&I Building: Ledger, 1973-1981 (Box 196, Folder 4)
      - C&I Building: Ledger, 1973-1981 (Box 196, Folder 1-3)
      - C&I Building: Ralph Rupley and Everitt Buelow, 1938-1980 (Box 196, Folder 5-7)
      - C&I Building: Insurance, McKinney Hotel, 1946-1973 (Box 196, Folder 8)
      - C&I Building: Tenant, 1951-1957 (Box 196, Folder 9)
      - C&I Building: Levit's Lease, 1010 Main St., 1951-1981 (Box 196, Folder 10)
      - C&I Life Building, 1953 (Box 196, Folder 11)
      - C&I Life Building, 1952-1959 (Box 196, Folder 12)
      - C&I Life Building: Everitt-Buelow Lease, 1959 (Box 196, Folder 13)
      - C&I Life Building: Diamond Shamrock Corp., 1965-1974 (Box 196, Folder 14)
      - C&I Life Building: South Western Bell Telephone #417, 1965-1975 (Box 196, Folder 15)
      - C&I Life Building: Gulf Coast Geological Library, #300 1006 Main, 1969-1979 (Box 196, Folder 16)
      - C&I Life Building: Federal Express Lease, 1981 (Box 196, Folder 17)
      - C&I Life Building Property: Levy Brothers Dry Goods, 1926-1932 (Box 196, Folder 18)
      - Darcy's: Statement, 1928-1929 (Box 196, Folder 19)
      - 1038 Main St.: Ellan's Hat Shop, 1956 (Box 196, Folder 20)
      - C&I Building Property: Main St. Lumber Yard, 1903 (Box 196, Folder 21)
      - C&I Building Property: Main St. Lumber Yard, 1900 (Box 196, Folder 22)
      - Full Block: Maps and Histories, 1916-1926 (Box 196, Folder 23)
      - Full Block: Map, n.d. (Box 196, Folder 24)
      - Full Block: Paving Certificates, 1927-1946 (Box 196, Folder 25)
      - Full Block: Purchase Proposal, 1953 (Box 196, Folder 26)
      - Full Block: Hotel and Theatres, Sub-Comtracts and Estimates, 1926-1927 (Box 196, Folder 27)
      - Lady Oris Hoisery: 1038 Main St., 1951-1973 (Box 196, Folder 28)
      - Lamar Hotel: Construction Proposals, 1923-1925 (Box 196, Folder 29)
      - Lamar Hotel: Loan Proposal, 1926-1930 (Box 196, Folder 30)
      - Lamar Hotel: Inventory, 1927 (Box 196, Folder 31)
      - Lamar Hotel: Store Room Lease, 1927-1935 (Box 196, Folder 32)
      - Lamar Hotel: Description and Statement, 1934-1935 (Box 196, Folder 33)
      - Lamar Hotel: KPRC Lease, 1934-1939 (Box 196, Folder 34)
      - Lamar Hotel: Store Leases, 1936-1953 (Box 196, Folder 35)
      - Lamar Hotel: Renovations, 1940-1941 (Box 196, Folder 36)
      - Lamar Hotel: Florsheim, Shoe Co. Lease,1026 Main St., 1945-1980 (Box 196, Folder 37)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1947-1950 (Box 196, Folder 38)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1949 (Box 196, Folder 39)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1949 (Box 198, Folder 1)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1950 (Box 198, Folder 2)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1950 (Box 198, Folder 3)
      - Lamar Hotel: Elevator, 1950 (Box 198, Folder 4)
      - Lamar Hotel: Gittings Lease, 911-13 Lamar, 1952-1981 (Box 198, Folder 5)
      - Lamar Hotel:, 1953-1959 (Box 198, Folder 6)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1964 (Box 198, Folder 7)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1964-1965 (Box 198, Folder 8)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1964-1965 (Box 198, Folder 9)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1964-1967 (Box 198, Folder 10)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1965 (Box 198, Folder 11)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1965 (Box 198, Folder 12)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1965 (Box 198, Folder 13)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1965 (Box 198, Folder 14)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1965-1966 (Box 199, Folder 1)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1965-1967 (Box 199, Folder 2)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1966 (Box 199, Folder 3)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1966 (Box 199, Folder 4)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1966 (Box 199, Folder 5)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1966-1967 (Box 199, Folder 6)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1967 (Box 199, Folder 7)
      - Lamar Hotel: Remodel, 1967 (Box 199, Folder 8)
      - Lamar Hotel: Lamar Club, 1968-1972 (Box 199, Folder 9)
      - Lamar Hotel: Russell Stover Candies, Inc. 1034 Main St., 1970-1979 (Box 199, Folder 10)
      - Lamar Hotel: Houston Shoe Hospital, 915 Lamar, 1970-1979 (Box 199, Folder 11)
      - Lamar Hotel: Houston Shoe Hospital, 915 Lamar, 1973-1979 (Box 199, Folder 12)
      - Lamar Hotel: Wormser Hat Co. 1030 Main St., 1975-1981 (Box 199, Folder 13)
      - Lamar Hotel: Newspaper Clippings, 1975-1985 (Box 199, Folder 14)
      - Lamar Hotel: Insurance, 1979-1983 (Box 199, Folder 15)
      - Lamar Hotel and Metropolitan Theatre Property: Note, 1915-1920 (Box 199, Folder 16)
      - Lamar Hotel Property: Loan, 1928-1939 (Box 199, Folder 17)
      - Lamar Hotel and Metropolitan Theatre Property: Note, 1921 (Box 200, Folder 1)
      - Lamar Hotel and Metropolitan Theatre Property: Note, 1922-1924 (Box 200, Folder 2)
      - Lamar Hotel and Metropolitan Theatre Property: Note, 1925-1939 (Box 200, Folder 3)
      - Lamar Hotel and Metropolitan Theatre Property: Lamar Hotel and Metropolitan Theatre Property: Construction Contracts and Notes, 1926 (Box 200, Folder 4)
      - Lamar Hotel and Metropolitan Theatre Property: Collateral Assignments, 1930-1931 (Box 200, Folder 5)
      - Lamar Hotel Property: House Construction, 1917 (Box 200, Folder 6)
      - Lamar Hotel Property: 910 Lamar- Ke7, 1919 (Box 200, Folder 7)
      - Lamar Hotel Property: Kanaman vs. Bankers Trust Co., 1920 (Box 200, Folder 8)
      - Lamar Hotel Property: Koch to Southern Loan and Investment Co., 1920 (Box 200, Folder 9)
      - Lamar Hotel Property: Store-Room Leases, 1921-1922 (Box 200, Folder 10)
      - Lamar Hotel Property: Store-Room Leases, 1923-1925 (Box 200, Folder 11)
      - Lamar Hotel Property: Excavation Permit, 1925 (Box 200, Folder 12)
      - Lamar Hotel Property: 99 yr. Lano Lease, 1926 (Box 200, Folder 13)
      - Loan, 1929-1964 (Box 200, Folder 14)
      - Loan, 1929-1964 (Box 200, Folder 15)
      - Loan, 1934-1972 (Box 200, Folder 16)
      - Loan, 1934-1972 (Box 200, Folder 17)
      - Loan, 1934-1972 (Box 200, Folder 18)
      - Loan, 1934-1972 (Box 200, Folder 19)
      - Loew's State Insurance, 1925-1944 (Box 200, Folder 20)
      - Loew's Theatre and National Standard Building: Architect's Certificates and Loan, 1927-1931 (Box 200, Folder 23)
      - Loew's Theatre: Lease, 1926 (Box 200, Folder 24)
      - Loew's Theatre, 1926-1929 (Box 200, Folder 25)
      - Loew's Theatre, 1926-1929 (Box 200, Folder 26)
      - Loew's Theatre: Lease, 1926-1952 (Box 200, Folder 27)
      - Loew's Theatre, 1926-1929 (Box 200, Folder 28)
      - Loew's Theatre Property (?): 1013-1015 Travis St. Homes, 1906-1924 (Box 200, Folder 29)
      - Loew's State Theatre: Box Office and Misc. Receipts, 1966-1972 (Box 200, Folder 30)
      - Loew's Theater Property: Note, 1927-1932 (Box 201, Folder 1)
      - Lamar Annex Hotel Building: Store Room Leases, 1928-1929 (Box 201, Folder 2)
      - Lamar Hotel Annex: AKA McKinney Hotel, 1950-1957 (Box 201, Folder 3)
      - McKinney Hotel: Name Change, 1954 (Box 201, Folder 4)
      - McKinney Hotel: Statements, 1966-1972 (Box 201, Folder 5)
      - McKinney Hotel Property: Elks Club Proposal, 1927 (Box 201, Folder 6)
      - Metropolitan Theatre: Floor Plan, 1925 (Box 201, Folder 7)
      - Metropolitan Theatre: Lease, 1925 (Box 201, Folder 8)
      - Metropolitan Theatre: Specifications, 1925-1926 (Box 201, Folder 9)
      - Metropolitan Theatre: Leases and Agreements, 1931-1952 (Box 201, Folder 10)
      - Leases: Metropolitan Theatre, 1950-1965 (Box 201, Folder 11)
      - Leases: Metropolitan Theatre, Gross Receipts, 1956-1969 (Box 201, Folder 12)
      - Leases: Metropolitan Theatre, 1967-1972 (Box 201, Folder 13)
      - Leases: Loews Theatre, 1956-1972 (Box 201, Folder 14)
      - Loew's Theatre: News Papter Clippings, 1972 (Box 201, Folder 15)
      - Metropolitan Theatre 192: Contracts and Correspondence, 1925-1931 (Box 201, Folder 16)
      - Metropolitan Theatre Property: Abstract Exam, 1906 (Box 201, Folder 17)
      - Metropolitan Theatre Property: Mulkey to JHJ, 1906 (Box 201, Folder 18)
      - Metropolitan Theatre Property: Notes, 1906-1916 (Box 201, Folder 19)
      - Metropolitan Theatre Property: JHJ to Southern Loan and Investment Co., 1906-1921 (Box 201, Folder 20)
      - Metropolitan Theatre Property: Tax Receipts, 1906-1921 (Box 201, Folder 21)
      - Metropolitan Theatre Property: Southern Loan and Investment Co. to Edgewood Realty Co., 1910 (Box 201, Folder 22)
      - Metropolitan Theatre Property: Note, 1920-1924 (Box 201, Folder 23)
      - North Half of the Block: 99 Year Lease, 1925-1927 (Box 201, Folder 24)
      - North Half of the Block: 99 Year Lease, 1925-1927 (Box 201, Folder 25)
      - North Half of the Block: 99 Year Lease, 1925-1927 (Box 201, Folder 26)
      - North Half of Block: Architect's Receipts and Releases, 1926-1927 (Box 201, Folder 27)
      - North Half of Block: Binz-Settegast Land Lease, 1934-1941 (Box 201, Folder 28)
      - North Half of Block: Income Statement, 1945 (Box 201, Folder 29)
      - Commerce Co. to C&I Life Insurance Co., 1951 (Box 201, Folder 30)
      - Purchase Proposals, 1948-1978 (Box 201, Folder 31)
      - Purchase Proposals, 1969-1977 (Box 201, Folder 32)
      - Purchase Proposals, 1974-1978 (Box 201, Folder 33)
      - North Half of Block: Binz-Settegast Land Lease, 1926-1933 (Box 201, Folder 34)
      - Miscellaneous: Save File, 1976-1981 (Box 201, Folder 35)
      - Proposed Sale, 1976-1981 (Box 201, Folder 36)
      - Sale to: Gerald D. Hines, 1981 (Box 201, Folder 37)
      - Sale To: Gerald D. Hines, 1981 (Box 202, Folder 1)
      - South Half of Block Abstract Receipts, 1925 (Box 202, Folder 2)
      - Various Buildings: Insurance, 1956-1973 (Box 202, Folder 3)
      - Insurance: Various Buildings, 1967-1984 (Box 202, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1952-1959 (Box 202, Folder 5)
      - 1015 Travis St. Leases, 1921-1924 (Box 202, Folder 6)
      - Abstract of Title: Lots 1, 2, 3, 6, 7, 8, 12, 1948 (Box 202, Folder 7)
      - Abstract of Title, 1914-1926 (Box 202, Folder 8)
      - Abstract of Title, 1927-1933 (Box 202, Folder 9)
      - Abstract of Title, 1933-1936 (Box 202, Folder 10)
      - Abstract of Title, 1936-1941 (Box 202, Folder 11)
      - Abstract of Title: Lots 1, 2, 3, 12, 1908-1923 (Box 202, Folder 12)
      - Abstract of Title: Lots 1, 2, 3, 6, 7, 8, 12, 1924-1925 (Box 202, Folder 13)
      - Abstract of Title: Lots 6, 7, 1920-1921 (Box 202, Folder 14)
      - Abstract of Title: Lots 7, 8, 2001-2011 (Box 202, Folder 15)
      - Abstract of Title: Lots 1, 2, 3, 6, 7, 12, 1929 (Box 202, Folder 16)
      - Abstract of Title: Lots 1, 2, 3, 6, 7, 12; 3, 8, 1926-1934 (Box 202, Folder 17)
      - Abstract of Title, 1934-1948 (Box 202, Folder 18)
    - Block 140
      - Contract, 1907 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Block 141
      - Correspondence and Contracts, 1912-1913 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Block 142
      - 918 Milam: Moving Contract, 1909 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Block 170
      - Various Documents, 1913 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Block 222
      - Correspondence and Contracts, 1911-1916 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Block 241
      - Correspondence, Contracts and Receipts, 1908-1918 (Box 203, Folder 6)
      - Deeds and Releases, 1920 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Block 248
      - Lots 4, 5, 11: Stebbins Property: (Sold 8/10/1966), 1950-1970 (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Block 256
      - Contracts and Correspondence, 1911-1920 (Box 203, Folder 9)
      - Improvement Certificates, 1916 (Box 203, Folder 10)
      - Keys: 1106 Main, 1917-1918 (Box 203, Folder 11)
      - Taylor: Rice Property Leases, 1917-1925 (Box 203, Folder 12)
      - Abstract of Title, 1920 (Box 203, Folder 13)
      - Contracts, Correspondence and Receipts, 1921 (Box 203, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Contracts and Receipts, 1921-1929 (Box 203, Folder 15)
      - Tobias and Simon Sakowitz Purchase: Lots 4, 5, 8, 9, 10 + 11, 1926-1928 (Box 203, Folder 16)
    - Block 268
      - Lots 6, 7, 8: Smith and Polk Cline Loan, 1916-1943 (Box 203, Folder 17)
    - Block 272
      - Kyle Building Property, 1862-1913 (Box 203, Folder 18)
      - Kyle Building Construction, 1913-1914 (Box 203, Folder 19)
      - Kyle Building, 1913-1931 (Box 203, Folder 20)
      - Kyle Building, 1913-1971 (Box 203, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, 1913-1974 (Box 203, Folder 22)
      - Kyle Building: Store Rooms, 1918-1925 (Box 203, Folder 23)
      - Kyle Building: Vannies Apartments, 1920-1933 (Box 203, Folder 24)
      - Kyle Building: Store Rooms, 1926-1930 (Box 203, Folder 25)
      - Kyle Building: Store Rooms, 1931-1937 (Box 203, Folder 26)
      - Kyle Building: Tenant's Furniture Sale, 1943 (Box 203, Folder 27)
      - Kyle Building: Tenants, 1948-1978 (Box 203, Folder 28)
      - Kyle Building Co., 1952-1957 (Box 203, Folder 29)
      - Kyle Building Proposal, 1953 (Box 203, Folder 30)
      - Lots 9 and 10: Lease Payments (Kyle Building), 1953-1959 (Box 203, Folder 31)
      - Kyle Building, 1954-1959 (Box 203, Folder 32)
      - Kyle Building: Income Statement, 1959 (Box 203, Folder 33)
      - Kyle Building: Stardust Gardens, 1959 (Box 203, Folder 34)
      - Lots 9 and 10 Leases Payments (Kyle Building), 1960-1966 (Box 203, Folder 35)
      - Kyle Building, 1965-1968 (Box 203, Folder 36)
      - Kyle Building, 1969-1971 (Box 203, Folder 37)
      - Kyle Building: Rent Receipts, 1967-1973 (Box 203, Folder 38)
      - Kyle Building: Appraisal, 1972 (Box 203, Folder 39)
      - Kyle Building, 1972-1973 (Box 203, Folder 40)
      - Kyle Building Sale, 1973 (Box 203, Folder 41)
      - Kyle Building Sale, 1973 (Box 203, Folder 42)
    - Block 273
      - Contracts, 1909 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Block 285
      - F. Ingrando Loan Lots 4, 5, 11, 1926-1954 (Box 204, Folder 2)
      - Abstracts of Title: Lot 4, 5, 11, 1907-1045 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Block 295
      - Refunding Certificate, 1900 (Box 204, Folder 4)
      - Tourraine Hotel, 1900-1926 (Box 204, Folder 5)
      - Tourraine Hotel, 1900-1926 (Box 204, Folder 6)
      - Contracts, 1915-1920 (Box 204, Folder 7)
      - Leases, 1919-1921 (Box 204, Folder 8)
      - Touraine Appartment: Commission, 1921 (Box 204, Folder 9)
      - Leases: 1315-1321 Main St. McAshan Apartments, 1921-1925 (Box 204, Folder 10)
      - Leases: 1301-1309 Main St., 1922-1926 (Box 204, Folder 11)
      - Leases: 1301-1309 Main St., 1927-1934 (Box 204, Folder 12)
      - Tourraine Hotel, 1930-1934 (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Block 296
      - Various Documents, 1907-1909 (Box 204, Folder 14)
    - Block 312
      - 1500 Clay, 1959 (Box 204, Folder 15)
    - Block 319
      - Lots 1, 2, 9, 10 Proposal, 1947 (Box 204, Folder 16)
    - Block 330
      - Contracts, 1907-1909 (Box 204, Folder 17)
    - Block 334
      - Correspondence, Contracts, and Receipts, 1906-1953 (Box 204, Folder 18)
    - Block 350
      - Correspondence, Contracts, and Receipts, 1913-1917 (Box 204, Folder 19)
    - Block 363
      - Correspondence, Contracts, and Receipts, 1899-1906 (Box 204, Folder 20)
    - Block 365
      - Various Documents, 1944 (Box 204, Folder 21)
    - Block 398
      - Contracts and Receipts, 1909-1912 (Box 204, Folder 22)
    - Block 406
      - Receipts, 1907 (Box 204, Folder 23)
    - Block 414; 417; 418
      - Deed of Trust, 1910 (Box 204, Folder 24)
    - Block 422
      - Contracts and Receipts, 1906-1916 (Box 204, Folder 25)
    - Block 432
      - Contracts and Receipts, 1906-1912 (Box 204, Folder 26)
      - Contracts and Receipts, 1918-1920 (Box 204, Folder 27)
      - Lot 1, 2, 3: 1915 Webster, W.J. Parker Loan, 1920 (Box 204, Folder 28)
      - Lot 12: 1907 Webster Ruth Jarrard Loan, 1920 (Box 204, Folder 29)
    - Block 435
      - Lot 7, 1950 (Box 204, Folder 30)
    - Block 437
      - Contract, 1911 (Box 204, Folder 31)
    - Block 441
      - Contracts and Receipts, 1904 (Box 204, Folder 32)
    - Block 460
      - Note, 1905 (Box 204, Folder 33)
    - Block 467
      - Improvement Certificates, 1924-1926 (Box 204, Folder 34)
      - Contracts, Correspondence, Receipts, 1924-1956 (Box 204, Folder 35)
      - Chevrolet Motor Co. Leases, 1927-1928 (Box 204, Folder 36)
      - Lots 1-5: Sale, 1927-1973 (Box 204, Folder 37)
      - Chevrolet Building, 1928 (Box 204, Folder 38)
      - Lots 1-4: Loan, 1928-1938 (Box 204, Folder 39)
      - Bonds, 1929-1938 (Box 204, Folder 40)
      - Chevrolet Building, 1934-1936 (Box 204, Folder 41)
      - Bankers Mortgage Co. Loan to: Posters, Inc. (Chevrolet Building, Lots 1-5), 1972-1983 (Box 204, Folder 42)
      - Abstracts of Title, 1892-1951 (Box 204, Folder 43)
    - Block 502
      - Bilao Purchase, 1924-1931 (Box 204, Folder 44)
      - Contracts, Correspondence, and Receipts, 1950-1960 (Box 204, Folder 45)
      - Lots 4 and 5, 1958 (Box 204, Folder 46)
      - Abstract of Title, 1914 (Box 204, Folder 47)
      - Abstract of Title, 1914-1958 (Box 204, Folder 48)
    - Block 557
      - Southern Parts Co. Lease, 1938 (Box 204, Folder 49)
    - Blocks 57 & 59
      - Abstract Lists, 1947-1951 (Box 204, Folder 50)
    - Blocks 57 & 137
      - Houston Property Corporation Loan with South West Straus Co., 1922-1941 (Box 205, Folder 1)
      - Houston Property Corporation Loan with South West Straus Co., 1922-1941 (Box 205, Folder 2)
      - Houston Property Corporation Loan with South West Straus Co., 1922-1941 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Blocks 58, 80, 137, & 139
      - United Property Corporation Loan with Southern Straus and Co., 1926-1942 (Box 205, Folder 4)
      - United Property Corporation Loan with Southern Straus and Co., 1926-1942 (Box 205, Folder 5)
      - United Property Corporation Loan with Southern Straus and Co., 1926-1942 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Blocks 70 & 139
      - Keystone Building Co. (Later: Metro Property Corp.) Trade with Southern Loan and Investment Co., 1923-1931 (Box 205, Folder 7)
      - Keystone Building Co. (Later: Metro Property Corp.) Trade with Southern Loan and Investment Co., 1923-1931 (Box 205, Folder 8)
      - Keystone Building Co. (Later: Metro Property Corp.) Trade with Southern Loan and Investment Co., 1923-1931 (Box 205, Folder 9)
      - Keystone Building Co. (Later: Metro Property Corp.) Trade with Southern Loan and Investment Co., 1923-1931 (Box 205, Folder 10)
      - Metropolitan Property Corp.: South West Straus and Co., 1924-1930 (Box 205, Folder 11)
      - Metropolitan Property Corp.: South West Straus and Co., 1924-1930 (Box 205, Folder 12)
      - Metropolitan Property Corp.: South West Straus and Co., 1924-1930 (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Blocks 137 & 139
      - United Properties Corp. Loan, 1927-1942 (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - Various Buildings and Properties (Box 210, Folder 1-25)
      - Appraisal, 1946 (Box 205, Folder 15)
      - Borrowed Furniture, 1942-1947 (Box 205, Folder 16)
      - Construction Estimates, 1923-1928 (Box 205, Folder 17)
      - Electric Services, 1911-1923 (Box 205, Folder 18)
      - Elevators, 1961-1965 (Box 205, Folder 19)
      - Financing, 1925 (Box 205, Folder 20)
      - Green Garage and Hotel: Specifications and Bio, 1913 (Box 205, Folder 21)
      - H.L. and P Agreements, 1905-1923 (Box 205, Folder 22)
      - Index to Real Estate File (Box 205, Folder 23)
      - Insurance, 1943 (Box 205, Folder 24)
      - Insurance, 1943 (Box 206, Folder 1)
      - Insurance, 1943 (Box 206, Folder 2)
      - Burglary and Robbery Insurance, 1952-1974 (Box 206, Folder 3)
      - Insurance, 1955-1976 (Box 206, Folder 4)
      - Insurance, 1956-1976 (Box 206, Folder 5)
      - Insurance, 1958-1970 (Box 206, Folder 6)
      - Insurance, 1960-1968 (Box 206, Folder 7)
      - Insurance Forms, 1960-1969 (Box 206, Folder 8)
      - Insurance, 1965-1981 (Box 206, Folder 9)
      - Insurance, 1968-1970 (Box 206, Folder 10)
      - Insurance, 1968-1981 (Box 206, Folder 11)
      - Insurance, 1968-1981 (Box 206, Folder 12)
      - Insurance, 1969-1970 (Box 206, Folder 13)
      - Insurance, 1970-1973 (Box 206, Folder 14)
      - Bond's Store, Houston: Insurance Policies, 1961-1973 (Box 206, Folder 15)
      - Bookhoust Lease: Insurance Policies, 1959-1983 (Box 206, Folder 16)
      - Chevrolet Buildings and Macatee Purchase: Insurance Policies, 1961-1973 (Box 206, Folder 17)
      - Carey and Mueller Purchase: Insurance Policies, 1953-1967 (Box 206, Folder 18)
      - 1114 Texas Ave. Building: Insurance Policies, 1961-1977 (Box 206, Folder 19)
      - Insurance Policies: Elm and Harwood (Box 206, Folder 20)
      - Insurance Policies: Electric Building and Hollywood Theatre; Fortworth, 1954-1969 (Box 206, Folder 21)
      - Insurance Policies: Electric Building and Kirby Theatre Building, 1956-1969 (Box 206, Folder 22)
      - Insurance Policies: Hedgecroft, 1955-1969 (Box 206, Folder 23)
      - Houston Bar Center Building, 1961-1972 (Box 206, Folder 24)
      - Insurance Policies: Houston Terminal Warehouse and Cold Storage Co., 1945-1973 (Box 207, Folder 1)
      - Insurance Policies: Kirby Building, 1959-1980 (Box 207, Folder 2)
      - Insurance Policies: Krupp and Tuffly, 1948-1978 (Box 207, Folder 3)
      - Insurance Policies: Kyle Building, 1949-1973 (Box 207, Folder 4)
      - Insurance Policies: Loew's State theatre, 1958-1975 (Box 207, Folder 5)
      - Insurance Policies: Mayfair House, 1959-1973 (Box 207, Folder 6)
      - Insurance Policies: McKinney Hotel, 1958-1972 (Box 207, Folder 7)
      - Insurance Policies: Mason Lease, 1951-1979 (Box 207, Folder 8)
      - Insurance Policies: Metropolitan Theatre, 1953-1975 (Box 207, Folder 9)
      - Insurance Policies: Montrose Block, 1956-1965 (Box 207, Folder 10)
      - Insurance Policies: 2400 Main (Texas Motor Exchange of Houston), 1958-1973 (Box 207, Folder 11)
      - Insurance Policies: Rice Hotel #1, Building- Fire and EC, 1960-1971 (Box 207, Folder 12)
      - Insurance Policies: Rice Hotel #2, Contents and Business Interruption, 1957-1970 (Box 207, Folder 13)
      - Insurance Policies: Rice Hotel #3, Drive In, 1959-1971 (Box 207, Folder 14)
      - Insurance Policies: Rice Hotel #4, Miscellaneous, 1947-1971 (Box 207, Folder 15)
      - Insurance Policies: Rice Hotel Garage, 1948-1971 (Box 207, Folder 16)
      - Insurance Policies: Settegast Leasehold, 1964-1967 (Box 207, Folder 17)
      - Insurance Policies: Simm's Purchase, 1959-1972 (Box 207, Folder 18)
      - Insurance Policies: National Bank of Commerce Properties, 1963-1973 (Box 207, Folder 19)
      - Insurance Policies: Texas State Hotel, 1957-1972 (Box 207, Folder 20)
      - Insurance Policies: 200 Madison Ave, New York, 1956-1965 (Box 207, Folder 21)
      - An Analysis of Risk and Insurance, C and I Life Insurance Co., 1958 (Box 207, Folder 22)
      - Employer's First Report of Injury and Statements- Katherine Martine, 1968-1974 (Box 207, Folder 23)
      - Taxes- Instructions (Box 207, Folder 24)